thrivelearninginstitute.com 2008-12-17

# Thrive Learning Institute

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Thrive Learning Institute website. On some pages you can make requests, register to receive materials, and update your eLibrary Account. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Business Name  
(etc.) 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide to better help our clients keep track of their online progress.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security** :

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information** :

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your eLibrary Account and editing your account settings. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us** :

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1-866-334-3672 or send us an email at [support@thriveli.com](mailto:support@thriveli.com).
